<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" ><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="4.0.0">Jekyll</generator><link href="http://localhost:4000/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="http://localhost:4000/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" /><updated>2020-01-06T22:39:27+03:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/feed.xml</id><title type="html">Latest Tech News</title><subtitle>Here we talk about the latest news happening in the tech industry: mobile, web, AI, robotics and many more!</subtitle><entry><title type="html">How to download videos from TikTok?</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/how-to-download-tiktok-video.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="How to download videos from TikTok?" /><published>2020-01-06T19:00:59+03:00</published><updated>2020-01-06T19:00:59+03:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/how-to-download-tiktok-video</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/how-to-download-tiktok-video.html">&lt;p&gt;A lot of you know about TikTok by now. It’s a video sharing service that allows you to upload your short videos, edit them and share it with your friends and followers. TikTok has been a very popular app for the last year or two.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Sometimes you come upon a video that is really nice and funny and you’d like to download it. How would you do it? Well, it’s really simple once you come by a service that allows you to download any TikTok video. It’d be nice if this service was free to use, convenient and fast. Luckily I know of such a service: &lt;a href=&quot;https://download-tiktok-video.com&quot;&gt;Download TikTok Video&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Just go to this TikTok downloader and paste a link to a video. After that hit that “Download” button. Your download should start in a few seconds.
Here’s hot the download interface looks like:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/images/tiktok-downloader.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;TikTok Video Download&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As you can see with this &lt;a href=&quot;https://download-tiktok-video.com&quot;&gt;TikTok Downloader&lt;/a&gt; it is now extremely easy to download TikTok videos on your PC, Mac or mobile device, such as iPhone or Android.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Well, there you have it folks - now you know what to do if you want to save a tiktok video! Just make sure the author of this video is OK with you downloading and keeping it. It’s tier hard work. Maybe it’s often isn’t that hard of a work, but a work non the less and the author should be credited for it!&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">A lot of you know about TikTok by now. It’s a video sharing service that allows you to upload your short videos, edit them and share it with your friends and followers. TikTok has been a very popular app for the last year or two.</summary></entry></feed>